Daniel Vieira Escudero

Calle Giralda, 6, 1D, Getafe (Madrid) (+34) 697 682 465 daniel.vieira.escudero@gmail.com



Profile

Responsible professional and compromise with my job. Proficient in english with international experience not only in software development, but also with management tasks, quality and testing throughout the life of the project. Total time availability, I can contribute with proactivity and responsibility, used to work and to coordinate in big and small teams.

Work experience

November 2019 - Present (2 years and 8 months)

SICE España, Alcobendas - Software engineer

 Development, integration and testing of the SCADA system for the New Bridge for the Saint Lawrence Corridor Project from Spain.

August 2017 - November 2019 (2 years and 6 months)

SICE Canada Inc., Montreal - Software engineer

• Development, integration and testing of the SCADA system for the *New Bridge for the Saint Lawrence Corridor Project* from Montreal (QC).

July 2016 - June 2017 (1 year)

Airbus, Illescas - Web developer

 Development of an internal website platform for the production control department of the A350 in the Illescas plant using python and Django, Git for the version control and Ms SQL Server.

Skills

- Visual Basic and C# for Windows desktop apps and C++ for the development of services with Visual Studio and TortoiseSVN (VisualSVN) using Ms SQL Server and PostgreSQL as database managers.
- Python for web development using Django framework and Git for version control. Experience using libraries such as NumPy, SciPy, SciRit-Learn, Keras, Pandas, TensorFlow or Beautiful Soup.

Education

January 2017 - July 2017

Associate Android Developer Fast Track Nanodegree by Google, Online - 240 hours certificated course.

September 2013 - July 2017

Universidad Politécnica de Madrid, Madrid - Computer engineering degree.

September 2007 - July 2013

I.E.S. Manuel Azaña, Getafe - High school degree.